<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="msg_array">
        <item>Genius only means hard-working all one's life.</item>
        <item>The man who has made up his mind to win will never say "impossible ".</item>
        <item>Cease to struggle and you cease to live.</item>
        <item>A strong man will struggle with the storms of fate.</item>
        <item>Living without an aim is like sailing without a compass.</item>
        <item>Live a noble and honest life. Reviving past times in your old age will help you to enjoy your life again.</item>
        <item>Accept what was and what is, and you’ll have more positive energy to pursue what will be.</item>
        <item>Behind every successful man there's a lot u unsuccessful years. </item>
        <item>Enrich your life today,. yesterday is history.tomorrow is mystery.</item>
        <item>The secret of success is constancy to purpose.</item>
        <item>Between two stools one falls to the ground.</item>
        <item>You have to believe in yourself. That's the secret of success. </item>
        <item>Success grows out of struggles to overcome difficulties.</item>
        <item>The dictionary is the only place where success comes before work.</item>
        <item>There are no shortcuts to any place worth going.</item>
        <item>You're uinique, nothing can replace you.</item>
        <item>Great works are performed not by strengh, but by perseverance.</item>
        <item>Until you make peace with who you are, you’ll never be content with what you have.</item>
        <item>If you would go up high , then use your own legs ! </item>
        <item>Do not let yourselves carried aloft; do not seat yourselves on other people's backs and heads .</item>
        <item>Keep trying no matter how hard it seems. it will get easier.</item>
        <item>True mastery of any skill takes a lifetime.</item>
        <item>The first wealth is health .</item>
        <item>Where there is life, there is hope.</item>
        <item>What makes life dreary is the want of motive.</item>
        <item>I have no secret of success but hard work.</item>
        <item>If you fail, don't forget to learn your lesson.</item>
        <item>I have nothing to offer but blood, boil, tears and sweat. </item>
        <item>Sweat is the lubricant of success.</item>
        <item>A contented mind is the greatest blessing a man can enjoy in this world.</item>
        <item>That man is the richest whose pleasure are the cheapest.</item>
        <item>You make the failure complete when you stop trying.</item>
        <item>Success often depends upon knowing how long it will take to succeed.</item>
        <item>Think great thoughts and you will be great!</item>
        <item>A man can succeed at almost anything for which he has unlimited enthusiasm.</item>
        <item>The only limit to our realization of tomorrow will be our doubts of today.</item>
        <item>One thorn of experience is worth a whole wilderness of warning.</item>
        <item>It never will rain roses.When we want to have more roses we must plant trees.</item>
        <item>No man or woman is worth your tears, and the one who is, won't make you cry.</item>
        <item>Each man is the architect of his own fate.</item>
        <item>Great works are performed not by strength , but by perseverance.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
